let myQuestions = [
    {
        question: "Which type of beans are used to make baked beans?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Borlotti beans',
            b: 'Haricot beans',
            c: 'Cannellini beans',
            d: 'Flageolet beans'
            },
            correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "What does IPA stand for?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Intensely potent ale',
            b: 'India pale ale',
            c: 'India premium ale',
            d: 'International porter association'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "Bobotie is the national dish of which country?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Nigeria',
            b: 'Ethiopia',
            c: 'South Africa',
            d: 'Kenya'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: "Which year did The Great British Bake Off first appear on TV?",
        answers: {
            a: '2009',
            b: '2010',
            c: '2011',
            d: '2012'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "If you ordered nigiri from a Japanese restaurant menu, what would you be served?",
        answers: {
            a: 'A type of dumpling',
            b: 'A selection of sliced raw fish & seafood',
            c: 'A type of sushi featuring rice topped with fish or seafood',
            d: 'A type of sushi featuring raw fish or seafood wrapped in rice and seaweed'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    },
    {
        question: "Which of these chocolate bars does not contain nuts in its ingredient list?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Snickers',
            b: 'Double Decker',
            c: 'Picnic',
            d: 'Toblerone'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "Which flower does the spice saffron come from?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Orchid',
            b: 'Crocus',
            c: 'Nasturtium',
            d: 'Poppy'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "A Whitby Bun is flavoured with what?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Raspberry',
            b: 'Coffee',
            c: 'Cinnamon',
            d: 'Lemon'
            },
            correctAnswer: 'd'
    },
    {
        question: "Gruy√®re is a cheese from which country?",
        answers: {
            a: 'France',
            b: 'Switzerland',
            c: 'Austria',
            d: 'Germany'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'b'
    },
    {
        question: "What are the two main ingredients in the dish Cullen Skink?",
        answers: {
            a: 'Smoked haddock and parsnips',
            b: 'Cabbage and potatoes',
            c: 'Smoked haddock and potatoes',
            d: 'Smoked salmon and potatoes'
        },
        correctAnswer: 'c'
    }

]